[{"question": " okay!", "answer": " come on, no peeking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " our eyes are closed and we\u0092re about to cross the street. very good.", "answer": " okayyyyy, open up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " what did you want to show us? because all i can see is this bitchin' van!", "answer": " yeah, it\u0092s for our catering business!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " i think i know that girl.", "answer": " all right, umm, we\u0092re not gonna really keep it this way though.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " no?", "answer": " no, we\u0092re gonna paint over the sword, and replace it with a baguette.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " and also, we don\u0092t know what to do with this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": "  remember that guy from cooking school i told you about that put cilantro with everything?", "answer": " oh sure, cilantro larry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " well, i\u0092m gonna fill in for him as food critic for the chelsea reporter.", "answer": " wow, monica! what an amazing opportunity to influence\u009a dozens of people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " how could you say yes, what about our catering business?", "answer": " oh no-no-no, it\u0092s only one night a week, and plus i get to take all of you out for a lot of free dinners.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " yay!!", "answer": " oh, in that case\u0097\u0097yay!  that was me hopping on board.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": "  hey, you guys! hey, ross, quick question for ya. are you ready to party?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, i could maybe go out for a couple of beers, but there\u0092s this thing about bumblebees on the discovery channel that i was planning to watch.", "answer": " no-no, i don\u0092t think you heard me. are you ready to party?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " nooo!! gandolf?! gandolf is coming to town?", "answer": " kathy\u0092s with her parents, i have nothing to do, so tomorrow we are partying with gandolf dude!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " dude, we are sooo gonna party!", "answer": " wow! okay, dude alert! and who is this guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " mike \"gandolf\" ganderson, only like the funest guy in the world.", "answer": " i\u0092m gonna call and get off work tomorrow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " i\u0092m gonna call after you!", "answer": " this is gonna be soo cool, dude, we never party anymore! chandler and ross: woooo!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " all right, were you guys smoking something in the back of our van?", "answer": " really. and what do you mean you never have fun anymore? you have fun with me, remember that time we saw those strippers and you paid me 50 bucks to eat that book?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " joey, you are gonna love this guy. gandolf is like the party wizard!", "answer": " well, why do you call him gandolf?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " gandolf the wizard.  hello! didn\u0092t you read lord of the rings in high school?", "answer": " no, i had sex in high school.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh, uh, joanna i was wondering if i could ask you something. there\u0092s an opening for an assistant buyer in junior miss\u009a", "answer": "  okay, but that would actually be a big step down for me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " well, actually, i meant for me. the hiring committee is meeting people all day and\u009a", "answer": " oh. well, i wish i could say no, but you can\u0092t stay my assistant forever. neither can you sophie, but for different reasons.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " god, i am so glad you don\u0092t have a problem with this, because if you did, i wouldn\u0092t even consider applying.", "answer": " really? well, in that case\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  and that\u0092s i\u0092m so glad\u009a there\u0092s no problem.", "answer": " that\u0092s fine, actually i\u0092m on the hiring committee, so there\u0092ll be at least one friendly face.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " ohh! that\u0092s great!", "answer": " you know, junior miss is where i started. oh, i had to sleep with the ugliest guy to get that job.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " no-ho-ho!  yeah.  i mean, no-no-no-no-no, don\u0092t you worry, i\u0092m sure with your qualifications you won\u0092t need to sleep with some guy to get that job. although, i might need some convincing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " well, i, umm\u009a", "answer": " kidding! god, i feel wild today!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh man! i am so excited\u0097i may vomit!", "answer": " will you calm down, he\u0092s just a human guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " look you don\u0092t understand, gandolf is amazing. y\u0092know you\u0092re never know what\u0092s gonna end up happening, you go out for a couple of beers and end up on a fishing boat to nova scotia!", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh yeah, it\u0092s beautiful country up there.", "answer": "  hey! okay! i got my passport, fresh socks, and a snake bite kit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " it\u0092s not gonna be exactly like last time.", "answer": " all right, i\u0092ll see you guys. chandler and ross: whoa-whoa-whoa!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " whoa-wh-wh-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!", "answer": " i have an audition, but i\u0092ll definitely hook up with you later. where are you gonna be around noon?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " somewhere maybe along the equator?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " what happened?", "answer": " he\u0092s not gonna make it, he\u0092s stuck in chicago.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " ohh, man! chicago, is sooo lucky!", "answer": " stupid, useless canadian money!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " you have a very impressive resume, ms. green. i especially like what i see here about implementing a new filing system.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " filing system? oh-oh! you mean those-those little colored labels you put on all the folders?  it certainly did brighten up the inside of the filing cabinets.", "answer": " well, they uh, they-they do more than that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " i notice that you\u0092ve been trusted with a lot of rather important responsibilities.", "answer": " yes, joanna really has been an incredible mentor to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh. and rachel has been really incredible in getting my morning bagel for me. it\u0092s amazing how she gets it right almost every time!", "answer": " i-i-i of course, i have more responsibilities than that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh yes, well there\u0092s the coffee too.  rachel can carry two things at once!", "answer": " yes, that\u0092s very good. now a uh, big part of this job is cultivating personal relationships, especially with designers.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yes, i realize that\u009a", "answer": "  and rachel shouldn\u0092t have any problem with that. the only problem might be getting a little too friendly, if you know what i mean.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i love working with designers!", "answer": " with them, under them, what\u0092s the difference? eh, rach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " hey! my first review is out!", "answer": " ohh! oh, the chelsea reporter, ohh, this used to keep me so warm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " all right, look at my on the back page.", "answer": " oh, okay!  \"would i go back to allesandro\u0092s? sure, but i\u0092d have to order two meals, one for me and one for the guy pointing the gun to my head.\"  wow! you really laid into this place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " hey, they don\u0092t pay me a penny a word to make friends.", "answer": " ooh, i gotta go. i found a guy that who could fix up the van for catering.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " oh! do you need me to go with you?", "answer": " no-no, it\u0092s okay. but are we sure we don\u0092t want the waterbed?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " haven\u0092t we made this decision?", "answer": " yeah, all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " bye!", "answer": " bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  who is it?", "answer": " it\u0092s allesandro, from allesandro\u0092s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " oh my god.", "answer": " i want to talk to you about your review.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " oh my god, oh my god.  call me on the phone!", "answer": " why? so you could hang up on me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " look, i-i\u0092m never gonna let you up so you may as well just go away.", "answer": " just give me a chance too\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  hey, do you need to get in? here you go.", "answer": " no! phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": "  i want a retraction! our food is not inedible swill!", "answer": " i couldn\u0092t eat it! i had five friends who couldn\u0092t eat it, and one of them eats books.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " well our service is not grossly incompetent.", "answer": " the waiter carried the breadsticks in his pants!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " well, you said that we except the discover card, which we do not!", "answer": " all right, that i\u0092ll retract. but i stand by my review, i know food and that wasn\u0092t it. you\u0092re marinara sauce tasted like tomato juice! you should serve it with vodka and a piece of celery.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " hey! i\u0092m proud of that sauce, it\u0092s delicious.", "answer": " oh my god! you own an italian restaurant and you think that tastes good?! where are you even from?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  lebanon.", "answer": " hand me those tomatoes, i\u0092m gonna show you what it should taste like! come on, hand me them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": "  umm, joanna? i wanna talk about that interview.", "answer": " i thought it went very well.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " no! it didn\u0092t! that\u0092s what i want to talk to you about.  now, just to brief you\u009a  i may cry, but they are not tears of sadness or of anger, but just of me having this discussion with you.", "answer": " rachel, please, don\u0092t make a scene.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " there\u0092s nobody here!", "answer": " sophie, get in here!  you see! now you\u0092re making sophie uncomfortable!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " she\u0092s not making me uncomfortable.", "answer": " congratulations! you now just crossed the line into completely useless. get out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " do you want me to quit?", "answer": " what?! what would make you think that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " wait-wait-wait-wait! you can put your sad little muffin back in it\u0092s drawer. if you must know the truth, i didn\u0092t want to lose a perfectly good assistant.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " that\u0092s why i said all those things about your flirting and your drinking\u009a", "answer": " my drinking?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " oh, i must\u0092ve said that after you left.", "answer": " said what? exactly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " that you enjoyed the occasional drink\u009aing binge.", "answer": " oh my god!! ohh, that is it! i\u0092m leaving! you are just a horrible person!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " wait-wait-wait-wait-wait-wait-wait-wait!! if you\u0092re gonna get all sensitive about it! i don\u0092t want to lose you. what if i, create a position for you? i\u0092ll make you an assistant buyer in this department.", "answer": " say more things like that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " you can have your own office, and a raise! effective tomorrow.", "answer": " i\u0092d need an expense account.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " done!", "answer": " and an assistant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " hey! what are you guys doing here? i thought you\u0092d be out partying with gandel-worf.", "answer": " it\u0092s gandolf, and he\u0092s not coming.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " so you\u0092ve been sittin\u0092 around here all mornin\u0092?", "answer": " no! i balanced my checkbook.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " yeah, and i-i gave first names to all of the foosball players.", "answer": " i can\u0092t believe he didn\u0092t come!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " so what if he didn\u0092t come! we can still go out and party ourselves!", "answer": " oh-no, y\u0092know with gandolf we\u0092d be out all night!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " yeah! we\u0092d meet, we\u0092d meet total strangers, and hang out with them!", "answer": " well, we could do that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " there\u0092s other stuff too.", "answer": " we\u0092ll do it all, and better! look, after tonight, gandolf will want to party with us, dude! come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " yeah!!", "answer": " yeah!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " it\u0092s not like we don\u0092t know how to party!!", "answer": " yeah! all right? let\u0092s go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " and may-maybe we could end up on a boat again? joey and ross: yeah!!!", "answer": " all right!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  hey-hey-hey, when uh, when were we on a boat?", "answer": " remember that really cold morning, you woke up and those dogs were licking your face?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " well, those were seals, man.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " hey mon, little question for ya! how do you think this suit will look on an assistant buyer?", "answer": " okay, the owner of allesandro\u0092s came over to yell at me, but instead i made him some sauce, and he offered me the job as head chef!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " oh my god!! you just ruined the thing i was practicing the whole way home, but i\u0092m soo happy!", "answer": " can you believe it? i finally get to run my own kitchen!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " ohh, you\u0092ve waited soo long.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " hey, pheebs, quick question for ya.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " how do you think this suit would look on an assistant buyer at bloomingdale\u0092s?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, it would totally depend on her coloring and\u009a  you got the job!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " yes!!!", "answer": " you got the job?! why didn\u0092t you tell me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " ohh, it\u0092s gonna be so great! i\u0092m gonna get to help decide what we sell, i\u0092m gonna have an office with walls and everything.  i\u0092m gonna have walls!", "answer": " okay, is this the day of good news or what? i got us a job! the wedding reception.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " ohh! umm, phoebe, i kinda need to talk to you about that.  umm, well i-i-i think it might be time for me to take a step back from catering.", "answer": " but we\u0092ve only had one job.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " i know, but now we have this second one and it just, it feels like it\u0092s snowballing, y\u0092know?", "answer": " yeah! what are you saying?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i got offered the head chef job at allesandro\u0092s.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " it\u0092s okay, \u0091cause y'know what? you don\u0092t really need me for the business.", "answer": " you\u0092re the cook! with out you it\u0092s just me driving up to people\u0092s houses with empty trays and asking for money!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " all right. but umm, i-i-i\u0092ll pay you back all the money you invested, and you can keep the van.", "answer": " for what? i can\u0092t believe this! i gotta get out of here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " all right, so we\u0092ll get a little coffee, and get energized, and we\u0092ll head back out.", "answer": " yeah, all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " so, we\u0092re having fun, right? chandler and ross: yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " we don\u0092t need that wizard guy. we hit a couple of clubs, talked to some strangers, and uh, after this, we\u0092ll head down to the docks and see about that boat thing.", "answer": " i\u0092m kinda beat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " actually, me too.", "answer": " are you serious?! chandler and ross: yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " thank god! i\u0092m exhausted!", "answer": " so you guys want coffees?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " yeah, but uh, i don\u0092t want to be up too late, so uh, i\u0092ll have a decaf.", "answer": " yeah, me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " actually, can i get some hot water with a little lemon? i think i strained my voice screaming in there. does it have to be so loud?", "answer": " i can\u0092t hear a word you\u0092re saying, my ears are ringing so bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " how sad are we?", "answer": " yeah, i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " y\u0092know what? we\u0092re not sad, we\u0092re not sad, we\u0092re just not 21 anymore. y\u0092know? i\u0092m 29 years old, damnit! and i want to sit in a comfortable chair, and watch television and go to bed at a reasonable hour! joey and ross: yeah!", "answer": " yeah! and i like to hang out in a quiet place where i can talk to my friends. chandler and ross: yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " and so what if i like to go home, throw on some kenny g, and take a bath!", "answer": " we\u0092re 29, we\u0092re not women.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": "  ohh, here you are. y\u0092know, i\u0092m-i\u0092m glad you decided to hear me out.", "answer": " okay, i\u0092m hearing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " i\u0092ve been doing a lot of thinking. a lot! and umm, well, i came up with a whole bunch of businesses you can do with your van. okay umm, you could be flower delivery person.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " or! a bakery delivery person.", "answer": " i wa-i wa-i wa\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " pizza?!", "answer": " monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " all right, i\u0092ve got a whole bunch of uh-uh, stuff in this area, but umm, i\u0092m getting the feeling that you don\u0092t want to deliver.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " okay. i\u0092m guessing that if you don\u0092t want to deliver, you probably don\u0092t want to pick stuff up either.", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " y\u0092know what, let\u0092s do the catering business.", "answer": " really?! are you sure?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah, y'know i-i made a commitment to you. y\u0092know what, it\u0092d be, it\u0092d be fun.", "answer": " oh! it will be fun! ohh! yay! oh! okay, ooh, let\u0092s plan the wedding reception.  wow! you really wanted me to do something with this van.  y\u0092know what, i want you to take the chef job.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " yeah. that\u0092s what you really want. yeah, i don\u0092t want to be the reason you\u0092re unhappy, that would just make me unhappy, and i really don\u0092t want to be the reason i\u0092m unhappy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " besides, it might be kinda fun to form the new a-team.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh, hi mrs. lynch! is joanna in already?", "answer": " oh my goodness! you haven\u0092t heard!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " heard what?", "answer": " joanna passed away last night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " oh my god! how?!", "answer": " well, she was leaving work and she was hit by a cab.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " oh my god! oh, i cannot believe it!", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " oh, god. oh, god.  oh god.", "answer": " i didn\u0092t realize that she was so close.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " yes, so close. mrs. lynch, i know that this is an emotional and difficult time, for all of us. but by any chance did joanna send any paperwork your way before\u009a it happened.", "answer": " no. nothing. imagine, if she had just stepped off that curb a few seconds later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yes-yes, just a few seconds and she\u0092d still be with us\u0097nothing about an assistant buyer?", "answer": "  no, i\u0092m sorry. i have to go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": "  good morning!", "answer": " oh, sophie, i guess you didn\u0092t hear about joanna\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " i\u0092m so excited about having monica come on board with us. although i do feel bad about having fired chef emillio, it\u0092s like losing a member of the family. of course, that literally is the case for several of you. tony, carlos, marie, please, tell your father how much we\u0092re gonna miss him. now, i know that monica has a lot of great ideas for this place, well, you all read the review. so without much further ado, i present to you our new head chef.", "answer": " umm, i just wanna say, uh  that with a pinch of exictement, a dash of hard work, a dollup of cooperation, we can have the recipe...  are you gonna kill me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep9.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}]